Quirini, Helen; Papers apap102
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Biographical, 1940-2010; Undated; 1; 5.2 cubic ft.
  - Kannenberg, Lisa From World War to Cold War: Women Electrical Workers and their Union, 1940-1955 (Box 2 (1-Biographical), Folder 11)
  - Kannenberg, Lisa The Paradoxical Impact of the Cold War on Women's Trade Union Activism: The IUE Experience, 1991; 1993 (Box 2 (1-Biographical), Folder 12)
  - Kannenberg, Lisa, Thesis with Chapters about Helen Quirini, 1990-1991; 2007; Undated (Box 2 (1-Biographical), Folder 13)
  - Kannenberg, Lisa "To Bloom where you are Planted": The Working Class Feminism of Helen Quirini, 1990-1992; Undated (Box 2 (1-Biographical), Folder 14)
  - Kay Raycroff and Sadie Fernandez, 1998 May 06 (Cassette 11)
  - Kennedy Grave, Old and New, Undated (Film 5)
  - Kennedy, Robert (Senator) - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 2 (1-Biographical), Folder 15)
  - Kid's Party, Undated (Reel 7)
  - League of Women Voters- Membership Information, Bulletins, Correspondence, 2003-2005; 2008-2009; Undated (Box 2 (1-Biographical), Folder 16)
  - League of Women Voters- Susan B. Anthony Award, 2003; Undated (Box 2 (1-Biographical), Folder 17)
  - Mohawk River, Boating, 2008 September 28 (Dvd 11)
  - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick- Correspondence, 1982-1987; 1990 (Box 2 (1-Biographical), Folder 18)
  - Music from Regional Conference, Undated (Reel 9)
  - My Interview, WWII, Undated (Video-tape 39)
  - My Movie Dream, Qurini Family, Undated (Video-tape 40)
  - News Parade, Castle Films, Undated (Film 6)
  - Nomination for Human Rights Award, Undated (Box 2 (1-Biographical), Folder 19)
  - Patroon Award, 1978; 1987 (Box 2 (1-Biographical), Folder 20)
  - Patroon Award, 1999 January 07 (Video-tape 41)
  - Phillipe Award, 1971-1977; Undated (Box 2 (1-Biographical), Folder 21)
  - Phillipe Award- Letters of Support, 1972-1975; Undated (Box 2 (1-Biographical), Folder 22)
  - Phillipe Award Submission Album, 1975 (Oversized 2, Folder 1)
  - Photographs of Helen Quirini and Assorted Others, 1954; Undated (Box 2 (1-Biographical), Folder 23)
  - Postcards Depicting Upstate N.Y. and the General Electric Building in Schenectady, Undated (Box 2 (1-Biographical), Folder 24)
  - Quirini all 8s, Undated (Film 7)
  - Red, Ricky, and Mike, Undated (Reel 8)
  - Reiki Certifications and Correspondence, 1994; 1996; 1999; 2001; Undated (Box 2 (1-Biographical), Folder 25)
  - Retirement Party, 2008 October 02 (Dvd 5)
  - Rozendaal, Kay-News Clippings, Correspondence, Memorial Booklet, 1991-1992; 2002 (Box 2 (1-Biographical), Folder 26)
  - Rudy Grad, My Topper Boat, Karl-Snooky Betty, Undated (Film 8)
  - Russel Sage, Miller and Quirini Discuss WWII, 1992 September 16 (Cassette 12)
  - Sadie Fernandez, 1998 January 22 (Cassette 13)
  - Schenectady Today, 1998 October 01 (Video-tape 42)
  - Schenectady Today, 1999 April 01 (Video-tape 43)
  - Schenectady Today, 2001 October 12 (Video-tape 44)
  - Schenectady Today, 2007 April 04 (Dvd 6)
  - Schenectady Today, 2008 March 20 (Dvd 7)
  - Schenectady Today, 2008 October 08 (Dvd 8)
  - Schenectady Today, 2010 March 11 (Dvd 9)
  - Schenectady Today, 2009 December 30 (Dvd 10)
  - Scrapbook I, 1964; 1970-1976; 1982; Undated (Box 2 (1-Biographical), Folder 27)
  - Scrapbook II, 1954; 1968-1974; Undated (Box 2 (1-Biographical), Folder 28)
  - Scrapbook III, 1967; 1970-1975; Undated (Box 2 (1-Biographical), Folder 29)
  - Sears, Ben-"The Schenectady Switch" Chapter Regarding GE, Correspondence with Helen Quirini, 2005-2007; Undated (Box 3 (1-Biographical), Folder 1)
  - Secret Love produced by Helen Quirini, Undated (Phonograph-record 1)
  - Side I, Finish 4th Meeting, Undated (Reel 12)
  - Skidmore, Emily Making "Room for Many Worlds", 2004-2005; Undated (Box 3 (1-Biographical), Folder 2)
  - Speeches by Helen Quirini, 1969; 1986-2004; Undated (Box 3 (1-Biographical), Folder 3)
  - Speed, Undated (Reel 10)
  - Speed, Undated (Reel 11)
  - Stratton, Samuel S., Correspondence, 1982-1987; Undated (Box 3 (1-Biographical), Folder 4)
  - Susan B. Anthony Award for Helen Qurini, Undated (Video-tape 45)
  - Susan B. Anthony Award Material, 2003 (Box 3 (1-Biographical), Folder 5)
  - SUNY Albany Union Films, Undated (Video-tape 46)
  - Tate, Sarlyn-Correspondence with Helen Quirini Regarding Edna Miller, 2007-2008; Undated (Box 3 (1-Biographical), Folder 6)
  - The Art of Aging-New York State, Senior Citizens Month Award and Recognition, 2005 (Box 3 (1-Biographical), Folder 7)
  - Upstate History Alliance-Interview Transcripts and Correspondence, 2003; Undated (Box 3 (1-Biographical), Folder 8)
  - Volunteer Recognition Program-9th Annual Recognition Reception, 2005 (Box 3 (1-Biographical), Folder 9)
  - Willison, Malcolm-Proofread Memoir Draft and Related Correspondence, 1995; 2008; Undated (Box 3 (1-Biographical), Folder 10)
  - Women of Achievement Award, 2007; Undated (Box 3 (1-Biographical), Folder 11)
  - Work Log/Diary, 1946; Undated (Box 3 (1-Biographical), Folder 12)
  - World War II-Helen Quirini's Activities, 1944; 1945; 1949; Undated (Box 3 (1-Biographical), Folder 13)
  - World War II Oral History Survey, 2004; Undated (Box 3 (1-Biographical), Folder 14)
  - World War II Notes for Autobiography, Undated (Box 3 (1-Biographical), Folder 15)
  - Xmas, 1974 (Dvd 11)
  - Xmas, Undated (Reel 13)
- Work, Union and Politics, 1933-2007; Undated; 2; 9.9 cubic ft.
  This series documents Helen Quirini's extensive union activities through her membership in Local 301. When Quirini joined this local it was affiliated with the United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers (UE). During the late 1940s and early 1950s, the federal government kept UE leadership and its members under surveillance because of suspected Communist ties. In his aggressive investigations of accused Communists, Senator Joseph McCarthy, chairman of the Committee on Investigations of the Committee on Government Operations, subpoenaed Quirini and she was one of many members of the UE to testify in a pre-hearing before Congress in February 1954. She swore under oath that she was not and had never been a member of the Communist Party. Citing these supposed Communist connections, the Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO) expelled the UE in 1949 and replaced it with the International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers (IUE). During subsequent years many UE locals elected to join the IUE, including Local 301 in June 1954. This series features materials related to all of the aforementioned events, including Quirini's subpoena, anti-McCarthy literature issued by unions, Quirini's surveillance files and a significant amount of propaganda from both unions issued before Local 301's vote to join the IUE.
  Quirini was very outspoken about issues affecting business and politics. During the UE/IUE switch, she was the only executive board member of Local 301 to oppose the move. A personal statement in the files explains her reasoning and disappointment with her subsequent treatment from fellow members of Local 301. Her many grievances in this series illustrate her advocacy for greater equality for women in the workplace and better working conditions for all employees. She retained many news clippings and materials discussing strikes she participated in at General Electric in the late 1960s and 1970.
  Quirini served her union during both the UE and IUE periods in many capacities, the extent of which is documented in this series through correspondence, reports, financials and other Local 301 business documents, conference proceedings, contracts, election campaign materials, newspaper clippings, photographs and notes. She held elected positions in Local 301 from the 1940s through the 1970s. Quirini was first elected secretary in 1947, and later served as treasurer and a shop steward. Her committee work included service on the social action, education and human relations committees. She attended union meetings and conferences and played for Local 301 women's basketball and championship softball teams when a young woman.
  In addition to her direct union involvement, Quirini engaged in several related projects. As an active and then a retired member of Local 301, she was a delegate to the Schenectady Area Central Labor Council and attended meetings. In addition to meeting minutes, reports and correspondence, there are papers documenting the education program about labor for Schenectady public schools that Quirini created as chair of the Council's education committee, in the late 1960s and early 1970s.
  As a labor representative, Quirini also served on the Schenectady Private Industry Council (PIC), part of the Capital Area PIC and was active from 1981 through 1993. The related files in this series record the organization's duties under the Job Training Partnership Act (JTPA) of 1982. The organization tried to implement JPTA through coordination and planning with business (small, large, minority), labor, and other concerned groups and ultimately provide employment and training for displaced or underprivileged job seekers and research and job-ready employees to private industry. PIC files include the internal documents of the Capital Region and Schenectady County PIC, such as meeting minutes, proposals, memorandums and correspondence, as well as documents relating directly to the JTPA legislation.
  Researchers also will find general labor literature from the AFL-CIO, UE, IUE and other organizations in the series.
  Please see Series 3 for more specific information on women's rights and representation in the workplace and the union and Series 5 for materials detailing Quirini's ongoing efforts to secure better rights and cost-of-living allowances for GE retirees, including those from Local 301. Researchers also should consult the finding aid for Local 301's records, APAP-023.
  - 50th Anniversary, Local 301, IUE AFL-CIO, 1986 (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 1)
  - 68 Porcelain UE News, 1954 (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 2)
  - 269 Committee to Save our Jobs, Undated (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 3)
  - 1946 Strike, Photographs, Undated (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 4)
  - 1966 Strike, Measured Time Work (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 5)
  - 1966 Strike, News Clippings, 1966 July-1966 October (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 6)
  - 1966 Strike, News Clippings, 1966 October-1966 November (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 7)
  - 1966 Strike, News Clippings, 1966 November-1967 February (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 8)
  - 1966 Strike, News Clippings in GE Schenectady News, 1966-1967 (Oversized 5, Folder 1)
  - 1966 Strike, News Clippings in IUE News (Oversized 5, Folder 2)
  - 1966 Strike, News Clippings in Schenectady Gazette, 1966-1967 (Oversized 5, Folder 3)
  - 1966 Strike, News Clippings in Schenectady Union-Star, 1966-1967 (Oversized 5, Folder 4)
  - 1966 Strike, News Clippings in UE News (Oversized 5, Folder 5)
  - 1966 Strike, Photographs, Undated (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 9)
  - 1966 Strike, Various Material, 1964-1967 (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 10)
  - 1969 Strike, Bulletins, Leaflets, Pamphlets, 1969-1970; Undated (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 11)
  - 1969 Strike, GE Schenectady News Negotiation Supplements, 1969 October (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 12)
  - 1969 Strike, Helen Quirini Notes (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 13)
  - 1969 Strike, History, 1987; Undated (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 14)
  - 1969 Strike, Newspaper Clippings, 1969 October (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 15)
  - 1969 Strike, News Clippings, 1969 November (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 16)
  - 1969 Strike, News Clippings, 1969 December (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 17)
  - 1969 Strike, News Clippings, 1970 January-1970 February (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 18)
  - 1969 Strike, News Clippings in AFL-CIO News, 1970 (Oversized 5, Folder 6)
  - 1969 Strike, News Clippings in Capital Area Labor News, 1969-1970 (Oversized 5, Folder 7)
  - 1969 Strike, News Clippings in Daily World (Oversized 5, Folder 8)
  - 1969 Strike, News Clippings in GE Schenectady News, 1969-1970 (Oversized 5, Folder 9)
  - 1969 Strike, News Clippings in IUE News (Oversized 5, Folder 10)
  - 1969 Strike, News Clippings in IUE News, 1969-1970 (Oversized 5, Folder 11)
  - 1969 Strike, News Clippings in Metalworking News, 1970 (Oversized 5, Folder 12)
  - 1969 Strike, News Clippings in Schenectady Daily Newspapers, 1969-1970 (Oversized 5, Folder 13)
  - 1969 Strike, News Clippings in UE News, 1969-1970 (Oversized 5, Folder 14)
  - 1969 Strike, Photographs, Undated (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 19)
  - 1969 Strike, Picket Line News, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 20)
  - 1969 Strike, Summary of Terms, 1970 February 03 (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 21)
  - 1973 Contract Negotiations, Photographs, Undated (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 22)
  - 1982 Strike Clippings, 1982 April (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 23)
  - "A Chronology of IUE's Social Action Programs", 1971; 1978; 1993 (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 24)
  - AFL-CIO, and House Voting Records, 1987 (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 25)
  - AFL-CIO, Comments on Proposed Regulations Governing Title III of the Job Training Partnership Act, 1988 (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 26)
  - AFl-CIO, Constitutions, 1995; 1997 (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 27)
  - AFL-CIO, Events, 1975 (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 28)
  - AFl-CIO, Fifth Constitutional Convention, 1963 (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 29)
  - AFL-CIO, Literature on Labor and Unions, 1966-2000; Undated (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 30-32)
  - AFL-CIO, Reports, 1970-1975; 1984; Undated (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 33)
  - AFL-CIO, Reports and Newsletters, 1970-1973; 1978-1980; Undated (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 34)
  - AFL-CIO, Union Counselor Training program, Leaflets, Fliers, Handbook, Agenda, 1985-1987; Undated (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 35)
  - The American Federationist, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 36)
  - American Labor Party, including Helen Quirini Candidacy for Rotterdam Town Office, 1949; Undated (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 37)
  - Bag Encouraging Shoppers Not to Buy GE Products, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 2)
  - Beirne Party, IUE Hall, 1978 (Cassette 14)
  - Boulwarism, 1947; 1974; 1991; Undated (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 38)
  - Brownell-Butler, 1954; Undated (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 39)
  - Buttons and Ribbons, Including Ones About the UE, IUE, Clinton/Gore Ticket, Shop Stewards and Scabs, 1978; 1986; Undated (Oversized 7)
  - Bywater- Fitzmaurice IUE Presidential Race, 1976; Undated (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 40)
  - Capital Region PIC, By-Laws, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 41)
  - Carey, James, 1959; 1965; 1973 (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 42)
  - Cartoons by Fred Wright, 1947-1948; Undated (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 43)
  - Catastrophic Mistake, 1980 (Video-tape 47)
  - CIO, Constitutional Convention Proceedings, 1948 (Box 1 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 44)
  - CIO Literature, 1947; Undated (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 1)
  - Citizens Committee to Support the GE Strikers Flyer, Undated (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 2)
  - Civil Rights in the Workplace, 1974-1975; 1979 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 3)
  - Communism and McCarthyism News Clippings in Schenectady Gazette, 1949; 1954 (Oversized 4, Folder 1)
  - Communism, General Electric and UE News Clipping in The Saturday Evening Post, 1952 (Oversized 4, Folder 2)
  - Communism News Clippings in GE Schenectady News, 1953 (Oversized 4, Folder 3)
  - Coordinated Bargaining Materials, 1969; Undated (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 4)
  - Coordinated Bargaining Committee, 1976; Undated (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 5)
  - Cornell Course on Labor Relations, 1971; 1978-1980; Undated (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 6-7)
  - Cornell Course on Labor Relations, Instructor's Guide for Reaching Steward's Training, Undated (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 8)
  - Correspondence from Ernest Kopper, President UE Local 301, 1954 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, "Planning for JTPA Programs Program Years", 1990-1991; Undated (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 10)
  - CPR Press Conference, 1998 October 05 (Video-tape 48)
  - Cuts, Cuts, Cuts: The War Against Medicare and Medicaid, 1995 December 15 (Video-tape 49)
  - Cutbacks in Planning, Methods and Time Standards Unit, 1971 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 11)
  - Discrimination When Not in Union, 1959 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 12)
  - Doris "Granny D" Haddock at the October 2001 Conference of the New York Statewide Senior Action Council, Inc in Albany, New York, 2001 October (Video-tape 50)
  - Economic Conversion as a Women's Issue, 1986; Undated (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 13)
  - Editorial about Discrimination of Non-Union Employees, 1971 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 14)
  - Electrical Union News Articles About or Mentioning Helen Quirini, 1948-1949; 1952-1954 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 15)
  - Electrical Union News Coverage of McCarran-Walter Immigration Act, 1953 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 16)
  - Electrical Union News Coverage of McCarthyism, 1953-1954 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 17)
  - Equality at Work: U.E. Efforts do Fight Racial Discrimination in the Postwar Decade by Carol Lambiase, Undated (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 18)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation File on Helen Quirini, 1993-1994; 1996-1997 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 19)
  - General Electric and McCarthyism Cartoons, Undated (Oversized 4, Folder 4)
  - General Grievance on Discrimination of Women, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 20)
  - General Labor Literature, 1955; 1967; 1976; 1981; Undated (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 21-22)
  - Grievance about Harassment, 1977 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 23)
  - Grievance and Complaint Review Procedures, 1980; 1982; Undated (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 24)
  - Grievance, Case# 437-70, Gender Discrimination, Includes List of Jobs Helen Quirini Held, 1970 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 25)
  - Grievance, Case# 5144-66, Contested Standards, 1966 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 26)
  - Grievance, Case# 5145-66, More Incentive Opportunity, 1966 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 27)
  - Grievance, Case# 5146-66, Request Time Studies, 1966 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 28)
  - Grievance, Case# 5147-66, Wrong Payment, 1966 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 29)
  - Grievance, Case# 5148-66, Station Allowances, 1966 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 30)
  - Grievance, Case# 5149-66, Change in Studies Times, 1966 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 31)
  - Grievance, Case# 5427-66, Written Breakdown on Set Up, 1966 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 32)
  - Grievance, Cases# 5433, 5434, 5484-66, Improper Payment, 1966 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 33)
  - Grievance, Case# 5483-66, Unsafe Working Conditions(Building 40), 1966 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 34)
  - Grievance, Case# 5485-66, Bargaining in Bad Faith, 1966 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 35)
  - Grievance, Case# 5486-66, Job Rate, 1966-1967 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 36)
  - Grievance, Case# 5676-66, Quality, 1966 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 37)
  - Grievance, Case# 5829-66, Improper Payment, 1966 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 38)
  - Grievance, Case# 5830-66, Elapsed Time, 1966 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 39)
  - Grievance, Case# 5831-66, Improper Payment, 1966 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 40)
  - Grievance, Case# 6509-77, Discrimination, 1977 April 04 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 41)
  - Grievance, Case# 8751, Transfer of Jobs from Piece Work to a Day Work Basis of Payment, 1964 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 42)
  - Grievance Procedure, Revised Draft, 1979 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 43)
  - Grievances, 1966 January-1966 July (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 44)
  - Grievances, 1966 August-1966 September (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 45)
  - Grievances, 1966-1968 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 46-47)
  - Grievances about Restroom Case, State Division of Human Rights and EEOC, 1979 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 48)
  - Grievances Blank Form, IUE Local 301, Undated (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 49)
  - Grievances, Case# 1527 and 5721-66, Polyseal Case-[RESTRICTED], 1966-1968 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 50)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Must consult archivist before viewing this material.
  - Grievances, Case# 9636 and 9637-78, Restroom and Gender Discrimination, 1978 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 51)
  - Grievances-Green Room, 1945-1946 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 52)
  - Grievances, Matron, 1954 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 53)
  - Grievances Transfer to Security Building, 1954 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 54)
  - Helen, Hank, Jim, Maureen, Brian, Undated (Cassette 15)
  - IAM-AFK Representation at General Electric, Undated (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 55)
  - IAM-Health Program, Information and Conference, 1972; Undated (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 56)
  - Incoming Correspondences-Support for IUE/UE Split, 1953-1954; Undated (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 57)
  - Inside the Plant Lost Time Vouchers and Receipts, 1966 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 58)
  - IUE Agreements with General Electric, 1954-1963 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 59)
  - IUE Agreements with General Electric, 1963-1973 (Box 2 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 60)
  - IUE Agreements with General Electric, 1973-1982 (Box 3 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 1)
  - IUE Agreements with General Electric, 1982-1991 (Box 3 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 2)
  - IUE Agreements with General Electric, 1991-2000 (Box 3 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 3)
  - IUE Agreements with General Electric, 2000-2007 (Box 3 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 4)
  - IUE Bi-Annual Social Action and Education Conference, 1983-1984; Undated (Box 3 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 5-6)
  - IUE Constitutional Convention, 1978 (Box 3 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 7)
  - IUE Correspondence, 1958; 1971; 1973; 1975; Undated (Box 3 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 8)
  - IUE District 3, Correspondence, 1965; 1867; Undated (Box 3 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 9)
  - IUE, Excerpts from By-Laws on Sex Discrimination, 1971-1972; Undated (Box 3 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 10)
  - IUE Fact Sheet and Backgrounders, 1987; Undated (Box 3 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 11)
  - IUE-GE Dispute Over Pay and Productivity Clippings in Schenectady Union-Star, 1964 (Oversized 1, Folder 3)
  - IUE-GE Negotiations, 1958 (Box 3 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 12)
  - IUE-GE Proposed Contract Benefits for 1985-1986, Undated (Box 3 (2-Work, Union and Politics), Folder 13)